The monthly explosion rate of Delta treasures is too high. This may be the latest one for Nigeria's African Star.
According to the treasure map in the official poster, it can be seen that there are a total of twelve points.
The location at six o'clock on the map of Longbow Valley is ready for everyone. Let’s look at them separately below.
Almost all points are next to the birth point. The first one is near the outer wall of Blue Port Pier;
The second is located below the abandoned village near the river; the third is near the left side of the small train station;
The fourth one is under the Super Star Station, near the current Crocodile Lair; the fifth one is on the outside of the checkpoint;
The sixth one is from the road below the hotel to the hillside; the seventh one is in the open space in the upper left corner of the small convenience store station.
The eighth is the mountain where Galbi was burned by fire. The ninth one is in the garden space near the hotel townhouse.
The tenth is below the waterfall. The eleventh one is near the pasture cornfield. The twelfth one is in the upper right corner of the radar station.
The current point description is based on speculation on the fuzzy map, and the actual location will be subject to the above line.
The official order is confusing and feels intentional. Will it be required to run the entire map in order?
There is also a collection of honey buckets. Will it be useful for digging for treasures? It is recommended that everyone stock up in advance.
Just in case. Are you looking forward to it?